I was very excited for E3, but the website I watched it on had been shut down...
...for selling fake horse semen...
So I had to,
Ahhhhh I could have just watched it on other websites.
I would have saved so much money.
I had to travel to Los Angeles and see it live.
Off to USA if you haven't heard about it,
it's where they shot all the Die Hard films.
My flight was alright until I found out that...
Scandinavian Airlines served Nescafé instead of any Scandinavian brands.
All scandies agree. This is high treason.
They are pissing on our flags.
Disappointment Immeasurable. Flight Ruined.
Instead of trying to improve my travel,
I decided to find out how bad this can get.
So I watched Justice League.
So I watched Justice League. On repeat.
11 hours, or five-and-a-half Justice League's later...
I landed in LA, and while I was landing...
...the first conference started,
EA.
Did I say first conference? I meant worst conference.
Started with Battlefield 5.
First trailer: Not very liked.
Kinda portrayed World War 2 as a good
time with your friends.
They also went: "How disliked can we go?"...
...and announced Battle Royale™ mode
and people actually booed. That's rude guys.
But still hopefully this will be
the only Battle Royale game at E3.
Move on to the most anticipated game of the year
FIFA 19
The big new feature in the next FIFA is that it will have a new number at the end.
Don't tell people you're making a game.
Have an intern make a logo.
Oh, poor Yarny, he's so out of place in his world.
Almost as out of place as this game at an
EA conference.
Huh? This looks pretty cool.
And we're back ladies and gentlemen.
EA, what the fuck are you doing?
We know what will get your attention.
(the wrong kind of attention)
Command and Conquer Mobile
because we don't like any of you.
This wound salting goes on for 13 minutes.
Finished off with Anthem.
I've seen little hype for EA's new
,probably super expensive, IP.
You know Ubisoft was like "Damn Activision is making bank from Destiny."
"Let's make The Division."
EA was like "Damn Activision's making bank."
"Let's also make Destiny."
But mate, you will never get the Destiny
audience of self-hating masochists.
The EA conference was special.
I missed the entire thing because
I got lost at LA Airport.
...but I did see a very nice Lexus.
It didn't take a picture, is it? Please trust me.
EA gets a 10/10
Minus 10 because it's not actually an E3 conference.
Next day, I'm off to the Microsoft Theater.
The media line is slow and hot.
I think Microsoft is attempting to kill all the
weak media people.
I wish I was confident enough to wear shorts.
Xbone Conference, I was still standing in
line when the thing started
Let's hope I didn't miss any announcement as I personally...
AH COME ON.
I don't think I've mentioned this before on this channel, but I'm actually a big fan of Halo.
Though, I genuinely hope that the new game starts with all the Halo 5 characters....
...dying from bad pasta.
Ori 2 - looks beautiful.
Needs a battle royale mode.
The new From Software game seems to have a clear story.
and that could kill this lore channel.
Todd!
Wrong conference mate.
(Country Roads playing)
I'm gonna hear this song so many times during my visit.
Life is Strange Spin-Off looks like something you would be forced to read in school.
Crackdown 3 is never coming out, give up.
Metro proves, once again, Russia does not
have summer and we all knew that.
Frozen is coming to Kingdom Hearts and we all knew that.
Would be a bigger surprise if Square announced.
No "Elsa Let It Go" BS in my confusing Disney game.
Forza 10, not surprising.
What is surprising is that they dumped leaves on people?
They weren't real leaves, they were made
out of Asbestos.
Five people died.
The biggest surprise is that they are working on the Xbox One: 2.
Let's hope it's cheaper, and also has a
terrible name.
Such is tradition.
Finally Devil May Cry 5.
It's been a decade since 4.
I see they've made it more realistic.
The conference ended with Phil very obviously setting up a huge final reveal:
A first person RPG with augmented humans.
Uh Oh, Square Enix's gonna sue somebody.
I wonder how much Microsoft paid for the reveal.
All in All, no real exclusives but a solid conference.
Xbone conference gets a 10/10.
Minus 10 for not waiting for me until you started.
Phil should have come out and told the
20 million people watching:
"We are waiting for Killian before we start."
Todd Conference.
There's a special kind of magic about the Bethesda conference.
The open bar.
Quantom Cola Vodka is pretty good
Also drank a Bud Light.
It was not pretty good.
Still had a great time.
Then it was ruined when I met the foul cretin...
...that stole Game Theorizing from me
and built an empire.
The second he saw me he tried to strangle me.
Todd saw the murder attempt...
...and to save me he started a conference
It started with them bragging how great last year was
Then the actual conference started
and they kept bragging
Then Pete Hines showed up and he also
started bragging.
There was live music
I liked it because I'm in the audience...
Intoxicated.
Rage 2 is DOOM meets Mad Max meets Borderlands.
Not a single person asked for this sequel.
But not a single person is mad about it
It looks empty though.
Doom Sequel, Demons have attacked Earth
and now their only threat...
...is one speedy guy.
Yeah, the martian demons are doomed for all eternity.
Now what we came for:
Fallout 76 is a Multiplayer Survival game.
Just like all the leaks said.
Still disappointed, but you can still play solo.
Although it's probably not fun.
There are currently hundreds of survival games on the market.
One good.
So personally, I have no interest in this.
Or honestly multiplayer in general.
I was still having a great time then they started talking about Elder Scrolls mobile...
and I really had to pee.
Then the conference became pure torture.
Whenever I see the Elder Scrolls 6 logo...
I am reminded of the pain.
Still excited for the game...
...that they probably started working on
the day after the conference.
The event ended with the screen turning black...
...the music starts and the Obsidian logo shows up.
Anyways now it's time for the after-party.
I didn't get to attend because I got kicked out.
I went to the bathroom downstairs and
wasn't allowed back in.
I kinda knew this would happen and I didn't care too much because I was very tired and Jet-Lagged.
So Bethesda gets a 10/10....
...minus a 10 for kicking out Diva Kilian Experience.
A new day, a new waiting in line.
Le Conference.
Ubisoft just stamped us.
I think they own me now.
It started with a dancing panda that
WatchMojo really hated.
PersonalIy I prefer pandas over WatchMojo.
Just Dance 2019 is coming to the Wii, yeah seriously.
A new Epic Beyond trailer...
...this time without swearing.
It's Open-World.
The word Ubisoft is French and
literally translates to open-world.
So every game kinda has to be.
Then a Finnish man showed up.
People thought this was part of the show...
...and not just some random Finnish man
The Division 2 - Summer Break!!!
Now you can hack and cheat, in July!
Introducing raids, we're gonna get to fight
giant soldiers with 40 people.
Skull and Bones looks like Black Flag minus 75%.
Is it just shooting cannons at each other? No exploration or anything?
Still more content than Thieves.
Starfox with...
...oh that's surprising...
Ancient China is coming to For Honour, would have preferred the Aztecs, or the Red Army.
Finally their biggest game Assassin's Creed Galaxy 2 the new Assassins Creed takes place in ancient Greece
Actual ancient Greece this time we saw Socrates and that's two generations from Alexander
so
How is Ubisoft gonna force Alexander into this?
I believe you can do it
all in all I give this conference a 10 out of 10
minus 10 because I didn't get a gift bag
went on a shuttle bus to the
Macintosh conference
I can't see shit, I can't hear shit
What I like about the PC conference is that the reactions are 100% genuine
Xbone has their E3 Prize winners and the Ubisoft conference is 50% Ubi employees
And at Bethesda everyone's drunk
At the PC conference. You can really hear the massive UGH
When they start to talk about star citizen, I watched the stream and you couldn't really hear it
Which is too bad because it was one of the top moments of E3 for me
Then a duck showed up
Then the conference ended with day 9 saying banner lords is never happening give up.
PrayStation
I wasn't invited to the PlayStation conference
I searched for who to contact and gave up after 5 minutes
Should have tried harder because this was terrible to watch from home
It starts with PlayStation coming out and explaining what the fuck is going on
That's not how you play a banjo ♪ Banjo Kazooie - Main Theme ♪
Last of Us 2 has a new trailer where a girl makes out with Ellie and that's it
I later asked naughty dog about it and they told me they got so caught up in writing this lesbian romance
they forgot about the whole apocalypse thing. Then the conference was over..?
Oh, no. It's an intermission
After 17 minutes, Sony. What are you doing?
50 mins later
It starts again with a guy playing something that is apparently impossible to play. What else is impossible to play?
That's when I knew they were announcing Bubsy 3D 2
Nope Assassin's Creed
It's literally Assassin's Creed
Control is about a woman searching for her missing TV remote
Kingdom hearts create the most confusing trailer of all time and is beaten after 30 seconds
My theory is that it's about a future where konami has eaten all the babies. This is gonna be MGS 2 all over again
Oh, yeah, it has gameplay. So now we know that
Finally spider-man a prison escape
I remember all these guys from the cartoon, but if Willem Dafoe isn't in it, it's gonna be a terrible game
Is it- Is it over now?
Yeah, Sony's press conference gets a 10 out of 10
Minus 10 for no one saying no to bad ideas
I guess that's E3 it's over and that is the-
The actual event I was at e3 for the first time feeling like I've forgotten something
WAAAH
Watched it on an E3 TV
They announced that every Nintendo character- except one -is coming to Super Smash
That's all they announced
Nintendo gets a 10 out of 10
Minus 10 because I'm biased, you see I was staying at the official Nintendo hotel
I literally met every Nintendo employee. I essentially worked for them
Here's a secret scoop met treinen in the elevator and he told me
"Going up?"
How can that not be a Smash Bros hint
Doug is coming to Ultimate
And we're off
I decided beforehand that today I'm gonna check out smaller games with short lines
So I ended up between Nintendo and PlayStation
I didn't have a map couldn't access the internet because Wi-Fi is $60. First game. I played was a random Switch PvP game
I destroyed my competition so they gave me a shirt
And that's why I flew 11 hours, not to see games. I came here for the free stuff
I got spyro sunglasses from the Spyro remaster couldn't actually focus on the demo
I played so much Spyro that I beat it without thinking
My biggest E3 surprise not a lot of indie games but a lot of chairs
Gaming chairs really need your own press conference
Another surprise was how big the Fortnite booth was and it really shows you how big the game became
After I made my video
after the three industry hours were over the plebeian-
I mean the general audience were allowed in and everything changed
I thought Activision were overestimating how many people wanted to play Destiny DLC
I was wrong
When I got back to the hotel I died
Day 2 try to stand in line for Skull and Bones
But it was like three computers and a forty minute demo next to us Namco Bandai opened their booth went there
and because I was the first person of the day to play Naruto
(Sigh)
They gave me a Naruto fidget spinner, this is the worst thing I own it's the worst thing anyone owns
Now I had todays game plan. Play Japanese games without a line
So I destroyed someone at Soul Calibur by button mashing
He seemed visibly upset
played.. uncanny valley
the new Megaman game had a.. too long line
So I played an old Megaman game
Squad Monster Hunter had a nice hype man
But I know what you really want to know about
Roast beef sandwiches. That's what they fed the media people
All in all pretty good day
Day 3, uhh
Day 3
"Kilian, that was a human hand you're a red panda."
That wasn't me. That was my Android learn Killian lore
I did day three different
The first day I showed up hours early, sat in the media room, drank coffee
Day 2 I showed up at opening time
Day three I showed up at noon
Drank beer and played Metal Slug
Guess which day was the best?
Today I was gonna play big games
Started with spooderman
Can't give you an accurate review because I've never been to New York
Then Tomb Raider
Can't give you an accurate review because I've nev...
Wait.. Yes I have
Square PR guy asked me if I wanted to play Kingdom Hearts 3
I said no
I saw Lexus and a Naruto fidget spinner
I didn't need more reasons to make people jealous
Went to a private showing of dying light 2
10 out of 10
They gave me a Fanta, I'm easily bribed
Never got to see Cyberpunk
They had openings but Projekt RED has barred me because I mispronounced
"Wódka"(Vodka) in my video
I did eavesdrop on an IGN profile talking about it
This person said writing is bad so stupid
I didn't have any Wi-Fi Let me eavesdrop on private conversations
I really wanted to say totes war China, but they were fully booked
So I started a hunger strike in front of the Sega Booth
They told me I could play sonic racing
That paused my hunger strike...
Then I chained myself so they would miss their flights
I got to Play total war.
My Hitman two rubber ducky told me that E3 was over
People were packing up and leaving
Goodbye E3, we all know what the biggest disappointment was
But who was the winner?
the winner of E3 two thousand eighteen
is uber for driving around all these lazy people to this line standing event
And that's the Kilian Experience.
♪ Purple Planet - Rickety Roadster (Theme) ♪ Thank you for watching the final E3 2018 video
Obviously this was my first time doing something "Vlog-esque"
so it might have some problems
But you know, I'm improving etc
But please like the video